[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Is it that, do you think, that is drawing so much attention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Well, as a matter of fact, Piers, that's an excellent observation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "I mean, would you advocate the death penalty in this case, Nancy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, Piers, this is my feeling on the death penalty -- there are certain cases that are so heinous that option should be offered to a jury.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nancy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Do you think we're going to see John Edwards facing a trial for which he could be convicted here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Well, he'll face a trial unless his lawyers plea bargain.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Edwards"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "So, in that sense, it is a donation to help him politically, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "That's certainly what the prosecution is going to argue here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Is it as clear cut as that do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Well, I think he's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Has this decision been taken for political reasons, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I think that's a legitimate question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Do people say that to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I think -- yes, it is something I've heard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Did it say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "I mean, do you see yourself as a sex siren?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Do you hate it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I don't hate it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "What's the worst thing about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "You know, the worst thing about it is saying the number.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "I mean, no spark?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Does it make you laugh now when you think back to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yes, it does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "RB", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Awfully satisfying, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "It makes me laugh now, but I do have to say there were 10 years between the age of 15 and maybe 25 that it didn't make me laugh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Because they completely crushed me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "You're having the last laugh, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "You could look at it that way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "And why, Ellen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I like them because, first of all, I don't think I'm supposed to be turned on.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ellen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I mean, I don't know how I'd feel about it now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Could you imagine doing a scene like that now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "No reason, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dennis Quaid"]}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Does it help when you've got some hunk like Dennis Quaid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "It helps when it's Dennis Quaid.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dennis Quaid"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Who's the sexiest man you've ever done a scene with of any kind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "That is so unfair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Was he really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "And we had a very graphic sex scene.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Tell me about your ex because you have a very nice ex- husband relationship, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "How have you managed to do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Well, we're both very sane people, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Is it unthinkable that you two could get back together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "We had a wonderful eight, ten years together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "A lot of people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Do you think that's the case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "The battle is not being won, which is why I'm so proud to be a part of this play now, because I think it's more important than ever that people are reminded there is no cure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "And I think, you know, what's there not to get angry about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Something so passionate, so visceral, has such an amazing connection with an audience night-after-night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "How can you go from that to a movie set, doing something that will inevitably be so trivial by comparison?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Sometimes it is, and sometimes it isn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 488, "question": "What is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "It's called \"Another Happy Day.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "On the whole, I'd rather be in Philadelphia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Philadelphia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "What do you think when you see that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I remember Jim punching the wall behind me and being a little bit concerned for my well being.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Why have you never been a wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Life has turned out so differently for me than I originally thought it would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "How did you imagine your life would look?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Do you think you'll ever get married one day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "I couldn't tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "What's happening right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "When you see friends who are married, do you envy them or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "No, actually I don't, in all honesty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Why are you laughing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "There's not much left with the bleeps, truth be told.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "But when you played the role, how much was absolutely you when you were going through addiction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Actually, my situation was very different from her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Yours was just alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "It was alcohol, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Do you ever miss alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "I don't actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Is that part of the way you win these things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Do you like doing interviews?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Sometimes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "What's happening now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "You're doing just fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Why are you blocking your ears?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "I am far worse than you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Is that what this all comes down to, that your life is never going to be right for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "No, it's -- you know, I like to believe that -- I can never hear myself the way I appear to other people, hear or see myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "When you look in the mirror, what do you see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "A person I've gotten to know very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Do you like her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Very much so, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "if things had followed a different path for you, when you think about the worst case scenario, where could you have ended up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "You know, had I not had the whatever, wherewithal, gumption to quit drinking -- I have a highly addictive personality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "Is that what it's like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Absolutely, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Are you miles more confident like many performers when you're on a stage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "For sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "Do you wish you could sometimes have that confidence in real life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "I like the mix up of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Oh, my heavens.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "Are you as happy now as you've ever been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "I am, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "Have you thought about your speech?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "If you win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "No, I really, haven't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "Yes, I have no -- I don't -- I have no idea.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]